{
  "task": [
    {
      "question": " ... and Noah ___________ with God.",
      "time": "8000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. taught"
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. walked"
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. ate"
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. served"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "b. walked",
      "type": "epi_4"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who was Noah's father? ",
      "time": "8000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. Lamech"
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. Abel"
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. Hunter"
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. Enoch"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "a. Lamech",
      "type": "epi_4"
    },
    {
      "question": " Which humans boarded the ark? ",
      "time": "12000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. Only Noah"
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. Noah and his wife and sons"
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. Noah, his wife, and Noah's sons and their wives"
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. Noah, Noah's sons, Noah's brothers, and all their wives"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "c. Noah, his wife, and Noah's sons and their wives",
      "type": "epi_4"
    },
    {
      "question": "What unit of measurement was used to measure the ark?",
      "time": "8000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. Cubit"
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. Meter"
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. Furlong"
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. Beam"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "a. Cubit",
      "type": "epi_4"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of these men was NOT a son of Noah? ",
      "time": "8000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. Shem"
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. Canaan"
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. Japheth"
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. Ham"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "b. Canaan",
      "type": "epi_4"
    },
    {
      "question": " How would the Lord destroy mankind during the time of Noah? ",
      "time": "8000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. Famine "
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. Earthquake "
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. Flood"
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. Fire"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "c. Flood",
      "type": "epi_4"
    },
    {
      "question": "Why did the Lord want to destroy man during the time of Noah? ",
      "time": "10000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. Man was too strong "
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. Man was too smart "
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. Man was too slothful "
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. Man was too wicked "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "d. Man was too wicked ",
      "type": "epi_4"
    },
    {
      "question": " With what material would Noah coat the ark? ",
      "time": "8000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. Grease"
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. Tar"
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. Animal fat"
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. Straw"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "b. Tar",
      "type": "epi_4"
    },
    {
      "question": " How many stories high was the ark of Noah?  ",
      "time": "8000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": " a. 7"
        },
        {
          "choice": " b. 3"
        },
        {
          "choice": " c. 5"
        },
        {
          "choice": " d. 1"
        }
      ],
      "answer": " b. 3",
      "type": "epi_4"
    },
    {
      "question": " What kind of wood did Noah use to build the ark?",
      "time": "8000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": " a. Cedar"
        },
        {
          "choice": " b. Gopher"
        },
        {
          "choice": " c. Nara"
        },
        {
          "choice": " d. Oak"
        }
      ],
      "answer": " b. Gopher",
      "type": "epi_4"
    }
  ]
}